open oven
take out gloves
take out pot
put pot on stove
close oven
turn off timer
pick up fork
pick up salmon
shake off salmon
put down fork
turn off hob
put down salmon
pick up pot
pick up colinder
put colinder in sink
take off lid
pour vegetables into colinder
put lid down
pick up colinder
put colinder on pot
put pot on hob
peel open fish
peel packet
pick up fork
put fish in bowl
throw away packet
peel fish skin
put fish skin in bin
turn over fish
wash hands
get soap on hands
turn off tap
shake off hands
pick up fork
pick up colinder
break up fish
stir fish
scoop out vegetables into bowl
scoop vegetables
pick up spoon
poke fish
scoop vegetables
put down fork
pick up pot
place pot on sink
place
rinse colinder
scrub colinder
turn on tap
rinse colinder
put colinder on drying rack
pickup pot
scrub pot
turn on tap
rinse pot
turn off tap
put pot on hob
turn on tap
rinse pot
put pot on hob
pickup fork
put down fork in bowl
put chilli oil on food
put down chilli oil
put soy sauce on food
pickup fork
put down soy sauce
put down chilli oil
pickup spoon
fish salmon out of pot
shake off salmon
put salmon on counter
pickup oven gloves
pickup pot
pour out pot into sink
turn on tap
cool down handle
turn off tap
turn on tap
rinse hands
turn off tap
scrub pot
turn on tap
pickup pot
scrub pot
turn on tap
rinse hands
rinse pot
turn off tap
pot put on drying rack
pickup salmon
peel salmon
empty salmon into bowl
put packets in bin
peel salmon skin
put salmon skin in bin
wash hands
shake off hands
stir salmon
break up salmon
stir vegetables into salmon
spil salmon
pickup salmon
stir vegetables into salmon
close chilli oil
open cupboard
put away chilli oil
put away soy sauce
close cupboard